Guide to the Photography pamphlets and ephemera, 1890-1950.
Photography pamphlets and ephemera
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Photography pamphlets and ephemera, 1890-1950.
8050
.5 cubic feet.
Printed Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes instruction and user manuals, trade catalogs, and advertisements for cameras and other photographic equipment and supplies. Some were issued by Eastman Kodak.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes instruction and user manuals, trade catalogs, and advertisements for cameras and other photographic equipment and supplies. Some were issued by Eastman Kodak.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Eastman Kodak Company.
Subjects:
Cameras--Handbooks, manuals, etc.; Cameras--Catalogs.; Photography--Equipment and supplies.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Ansco Company, 1911 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Bell & Howell Company, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Cameragraph Company, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Defender Photo Supply Company, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Eastman Kodak Company, 1930-1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Eastman Kodak instruction publications, 1909-1937 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Eastman Kodak product catalogs, 1895-1938 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Folmer Graflex Company, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- General Electric Company photo bulbs, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Housh albums, photo mountings, calendars, and frames, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Kalart Company: micromatic speed flash, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Lafayette Camera Division of Radio Wire Television, Inc., 1940 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Leica, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Selvaggio Accordion Band, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Shepard Cameras, photographic apparatus and supplies, 1908-1909 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Vaporate: Peerless Film Treatment, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Kodak: Premo camera and general photographic equipment, 1917-1918 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Photostat Corporation: Photostat recording equipment, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)